export default data = [
  {
      question: "Mr. Lin is a very ________ writer; he publishes at least five novels every year.",
      options: ["moderate","temporary","productive","reluctant"],
      correct_option: "productive"
  },
  {
      question: "Using a heating pad or taking warm baths can sometimes help to _____ pain in the lower back.",
      options: ["polish","relieve","switch","maintain"],
      correct_option: "relieve"
  },
  {
      question: "Peter stayed up late last night, so he drank a lot of coffee this morning to keep himself _____ in class.",
      options: ["acceptable","amazed","accurate","awake"],
      correct_option: "awake"
  },
  {
      question: "Due to _______, prices for daily necessities have gone up and we have to pay more for the same items now.",
      options: ["inflation","solution","objection","condition"],
      correct_option: "inflation"
  },
  {
      question: "The government is doing its best to ____ the cultures of the tribal people for fear that they may soon die out.",
      options: ["preserve","frustrate","hesitate","overthrow"],
      correct_option: "preserve"
  },
  {
      question: "I could not ______ the sweet smell from the bakery, so I walked in and bought a fresh loaf of bread.",
      options: ["insist","resist","obtain","contain"],
      correct_option: "resist"
  },
  {
      question: "Steve has several meetings to attend every day; therefore, he has to work on a very _____ schedule.",
      options: ["dense","various","tight","current"],
      correct_option: "tight"
  },
  {
      question: "Michael Phelps, an American swimmer, broke seven world records and won eight gold medals in menâ€™s swimming _____ in the 2008 Olympics.",
      options: ["drills","techniques","routines","contests"],
      correct_option: "contests"
  },
  {
      question: "Those college students work at the orphanage on a _____ basis, helping the children with their studies without receiving any pay.",
      options: ["voluntary","competitive","sorrowful","realistic"],
      correct_option: "voluntary"
  },
  {
      question: "Studies show that asking children to do house _____, such as taking out the trash or doing the dishes, helps them grow into responsible adults.",
      options: ["missions","chores","approaches","incidents"],
      correct_option: "chores"
  },
  {
      question: "John has been scolded by his boss for over ten minutes now. _____, she is not happy about his being late again.",
      options: ["Expressively","Apparently","Immediately","Originally"],
      correct_option: "Apparently"
  },
  {
      question: "Since the orange trees suffered _____ damage from a storm in the summer, the farmers are expecting a sharp decline in harvests this winter.",
      options: ["potential","relative","severe","mutual"],
      correct_option: "severe"
  },
  {
      question: "Typhoon Morakot claimed more than six hundred lives in early August of 2009, making it the most serious natural _____ in Taiwan in recent decades.",
      options: ["disaster","barrier","anxiety","collapse"],
      correct_option: "disaster"
  },
  {
      question: "Robert was the only _____ to the car accident. The police had to count on him to find out exactly how the accident happened.",
      options: ["dealer","guide","witness","client"],
      correct_option: "witness"
  },
  {
      question: "Badly injured in the car accident, Jason could _____ move his legs and was sent to the hospital right away.",
      options: ["accordingly","undoubtedly","handily","scarcely"],
      correct_option: "scarcely"
  },
]
